Total Experience: 2 Year(s) 0 Month(s)

Notice Period: 2 Months

Highest Degree: B.Tech/B.E. [Electronics/Telecommunication]



Software Development Engineer-Test seeking roles in Software
Development, Application Programming, Web Development, Client
Management, Software Testing, Requirement Gathering, Algorithm Development, Core
Java, Hibernate, Spring, Mayen, GIT, Github



Current Designation: Software Development Engineer in Test

Current Company: Mobikwik
Current Location: Gurgaon

Pref. Location: Bengaluru / Bangalore, Delhi / NCR, Hyderabad

Functional Area: IT Software - Application Programming /

Maintenance

Role: Software Developer

Industry: IT-Software/Software Services

Marital Status: Single/unmarried

Key Skills: Software Development Engineer-Test, Software Developer, Software Development, Application Programming, Web Development, Client Management, Software Testing, Requirement Gathering, Algorithm

Development, Core Java, Hibernate, Spring, Maven, GIT, Github

Verified: Phone Number | Email - id

Last Active: 22-Jan-21 Last Modified: 22-Jan-21

Summary

Experienced in developing products for complete E-Kyc(Document verification) of customers and payment interface which included

facilities like self onboarding of merchants and includes various modules containing various offers and payment option flexibility for

easy and hassle-free payment option for customers.

Work Experience

Mobikwik as Software Development Engineer in Test Jun 2019 to Till Date

One Mobikwik Systems Pvt. Ltd. as Software Development Engineer in Test Jun 2019 to Jun 2019

Helped develop a complete module from scratch for E- KYC of Customers through online verification of customer documents like aadhaar card, pan card, etc. within seconds with effortless user experience.

Workplace, Company as Project - Designing of Controller for Solid State Transformer Jul 2018 to Apr 2019

Education

UG: B.Tech/B.E. (Electronics/Telecommunication) from Hbti, Kanpur Nagar in 2019

IT Skills

Skill Name	Version Last Used	Experience
C & C++		
CORE JAVA		
Data Structure And Algorithms		
Spring		
Hibernate		
Git and Github		
MAVEN		
TestNG framework		
Postman and api testing	2020	1 Year(s) 6 Month(s)

Languages Known

Language	Proficiency	Read	Write	Speak
English	Proficient			
Hindi	Proficient			

Affirmative Action

Job Type: Permanent

Physically Challenged: No

Category: General

Employment Status: Full time

Work Authorization